I can't let you do this.
I love him, Dad.
Because of Liam.
I hold on to my life
because of what he made me feel.
Bad day? It feels good to breathe!
- It feels good to breathe!
- More!
- That's it!
- Hi, Maxine.
You look good.
Well, congrats.
I heard they're considering you
to star in the new prime time show.
This will be your big break.
Yes, Sir Pao.
You know how showbiz is.
Everyone has his own time.
Where's Sir Liam? So you can go home.
Miss Joyce, I was with Sir Liam
outside earlier
while waiting for the props.
But when I returned to greet the suppliers,
Sir Liam wasn't there anymore.
Lift him up.
Call the medic!
Medic!
- Via!
- Spoiled brat!
Dad, please. Don't, no, please.
I love him!
From now on,
you are no longer connected
in any of my businesses.
I was kicked out from
the Herrera Group of Companies.
I'm no longer part of Blacksmith.
I can't go back to Casa Fuerte either.
What about our film?
I have no choice but to start over again.
Why don't we make our own film?
On one condition.
Part of what we'll make from the movie
will go to this orphanage.
I won't say no to that.
- Deal?
- Deal.
What's the occasion?
Someone special is coming over.
Too bad Borj isn't here.
I cooked a lot.
Special? It looks special, son.
It has lots of onions.
Onions are expensive nowadays.
So, special, huh? Who is it?
Nothing. Just a guest, Mom.
Just a guest.
It's just a colleague.
My colleague.
- Colleague?
- Yes.
Colleague?
Smells like you showered in perfume.
Is it really just a colleague?
Hello!
- Oh, hello!
- Wow, lots of food...
Yes.
How are you?
- This is Queenie, Auntie.
- Yes.
- Hello, Queenie.
- Hello, Ma'am Tess.
- Right...
- What's the occasion?
So that's why my son showered in perfume.
It's because you're coming.
He even cooked for you.
Look at that.
I remember the young love, sweet love.
What's the occasion?
Wait, don't you know about this, Via?
No. Is this a surprise?
Who's the special guest?
Special?
Anybody home?
Sorry, we let ourselves in
because your door is open.
- Sorry, Auntie.
- Joyce.
Hi, Aunt Tess.
It's okay.
Via.
Come on in. Come in.
We welcome ourselves.
Oh, I have a gift for you.
- For me?
- Yes. Here.
This is for good luck,
good life, and long life.
Oh?
- Wow!
- What's your year?
- Horse.
- Oh, horse.
- Wow.
- Hold on.
Ma'am Tess, be careful with...
Horses!
- Really?
- Yes, with horses...
- Horses?
- I mean with an ironing board.
Let's save the jokes for later, Odet.
We should eat first.
So, you're the special guest.
That's why Liam was so busy.
He couldn't even answer my call.
You're lucky.
Auntie Tess is the one who usually cooks.
Right, Auntie?
It's his first time cooking.
My boyfriend has never cooked for me.
I hope you don't get a stomach ache.
I don't think so.
Did you cook a lot, Liam?
Why? Are there other people coming?
Is Hans with you?
Hi!
Hello.
What are you guys doing here?
Liam...
Like me...
They also can't leave you.
Let's continue our project.
We're all here because we all agreed.
We were off to a good start.
Right, guys?
But VLH called it trash.
He wanted to brings things back
to the old formula...
Blacksmith producing action films.
What will happen
to the sequences already shot?
Miss Joyce paid for all of it.
Let's not talk about money.
Let's just charge it to experience.
That experience is so expensive.
So, Liam...
Are you game?
As long as it's not for propaganda.
I mean...
I know you're concerned
about the elections, Josh, but...
I know you're going to say that.
So I already prepared an answer.
This time...
we don't have to rush or finish
before the elections.
We can release it after the elections, right?
Sir Liam,
maybe this can help us not become unemployed.
If everything is all good...
Then, game!
- Right?
- That's what we want to hear.
What else is missing?
Your work.
New story, Liam.
Do you already have an idea?
Love story.
Cake?
Yes, please.
Do you want some, too?
- Yes?
- Sure.
Try it. Come on. Try it first.
- I got it. Let me.
- Come on.
Oops, I'm sorry.
Well, actually, this concept isn't new.
I mean, most of us want a love story.
A story that has...
What else could it be?
A happy... ending.
But...
does the story really end here?
I mean, for example...
When both sides of the family
already agree to the forbidden love
of our heroes...
Or, if the leading man catches up
with the woman at the airport
right before she leaves...
Or when they already said their vows
at the altar...
What's next to their love story?
What really happens after happily ever after?
That won't be easy, Sir.
You know why?
I will show you what will happen
after the happily ever after.
Let's go, Megan. Come with me.
Just come with me.
Me?
Okay, let's see.
Stay here.
Watch this.
Babe, come on. Just once.
Stop messing with me.
Come on, Babe.
Let's make love.
Let's give our son a sibling. Come on.
Let's go, Babe.
Hey, Leopoldo.
How dare you.
You don't give enough money
for diapers and milk.
And now, you want another child?
End scene.
See?
The story arc is so drastic.
Before, they would kiss each other
the moment they touched.
But now, look at what happened.
Or it can also be like this.
In the first act, their hearts beat faster...
from fear.
Hurry up! The zombies are coming!
Love...
Go on and run.
Leave me here.
- No.
- Go.
- Hurry, go!
- I won't leave you. I love you so much.
Did you get bitten?
He got bitten.
Me, too! I want to get bitten!
I want to get bitten.
That's enough.
Stop. Cut! Cut!
- End scene.
- I love it!
I got carried away.
- It's good.
- That's it.
Nice. We can do that.
- Nice!
- That's good. That's okay.
I love it.
Sir Liam, I'm sure Joyce has ideas too.
Go on, Sis. Come on. Pitch your ideas.
- We're just the only ones here.
- No.
- Go on.
- Why me?
Go, sis. Show them your acting prowess.
Go, Joyce.
- Go, Joyce.
They say...
They say, if...
if two people can't grow together, they...
they grow apart.
I thought it wouldn't happen to us.
I won't regret that
we did not give up until the end.
Even in the next life...
or in the life after that...
I will still love you.
I still love you so much.
Even though in the end...
That's all.
Beautiful.
You really are something, Sis.
You have my vote, sis.
But if happily ever after doesn't exist...
He can still find new love.
Right, Love?
But if happily ever after doesn't exist...
He can still find new love.
Right, Love?
For me, love is a choice.
If it doesn't work out with someone,
you can always choose
to be happy with someone else.
I agree.
As long as you are breathing, there's hope.
So...
Love triangle?
Why not?
But he should... stand by his new love.
It's toxic.
They keep trying even if they get hurt
over and over again.
So the hero will end up with his new love?
Sorry, I just got carried away.
That's nice.
- That's good.
- Woman empowerment, right?
If it's a story about women,
the woman will be happy even if she's alone.
She's free.
She will let the two be happy.
I love it.
I love it too.
We'll teach about self-love.
But at the same time,
the value of commitment.
What do you think, Sir Liam?
All your ideas are valid.
But I guess...
the central theme of our story...
will be about second chances.
I mean, when it comes to relationships,
there will be problems.
Challenges...
But we will show how they will face it...
together.
Dance your heart out?
This is all I could give, Joyce.
You can do it.
Miss Lemon...
Miss Lemon, thank you so much
for letting us pitch our concept
to you and to Miss Charry for DigiTV.
Oh, come on. I love your story, Joyce.
And I love your script, Liam.
Gosh! Love it, love it, love it!
Because I lived it!
It's so painful.
You know, it's painful but heartwarming, too.
Miss Charry's just in Singapore right now.
But she wanted you to know that
she could relate to your story.
Thank you.
You know, guys, we at DigiTV are down
for great Filipino love stories.
Especially "What Happens
After Happily Ever After"?
Millennials and Gen Z
will definitely watch it.
And that's what the young viewers like.
But... just an idea.
Why don't we put
an out-of-the-country element?
Let's go out of the Philippines,
so we can reach the Filipinos abroad.
Why? Budget concerns?
Don't worry.
We'll talk to the embassy
of whatever country you'll choose
so we can save some money, right?
Miss Lemon, thank you so much.
You are heaven-sent to us.
Actually, Miss Lemon,
our concept is flexible.
It will still work even if we transpose it
to another place.
Don't worry.
We'll adjust the script
and we'll get back to you.
Now you're talking.
Miss Lemon... thank you so much.
It's been my dream to make a film on DigiTV.
Come on. It's my pleasure.
But I only have one request.
- What is it?
Can you make one of my artists
part of your film?
Who is it, Miss Lemon?
Oh, you know her very well.
It's Maxine.
Sorry.
Do you have an issue?
Not at all, Miss Lemon.
We don't have any issues.
Actually, it's perfect, Miss Lemon.
We're looking for another female lead
because it's a love triangle...
Then that's it!
That's great.
Stay there.
This is just a warm-up.
Come on. Join us.
- Game.
- This is just a warm-up?
Yes.
There. There.
So this is just a warm-up, Joyce.
Turn, turn, turn.
I'm sweating profusely, Joyce.
Just do it.
We don't want to lose our project.
- Lower.
- Lower?
So we're going down.
There, lower.
- Lower? Lower?
- Yes, yes.
- It hurts my knees.
- Good job!
Sway. Shake your hips.
Sway?
- A lot is happening.
- One, two, three, four.
One, two, three, four.
There you go.
Have you been waiting long?
You're quiet.
Where is the man we're going to meet?
Why are you here?
Where's Pogi?
From now on, I will get your remittance.
- Congressman sent me...
- He gave him the go signal.
Make sure it's safe.
We don't want the chief to get in trouble.
You can trust me.
Boss, I'm begging you.
Boss, I have a family.
Boss, I won't talk.
Wait, don't!
If my brother learns that someone saw us,
we'll be dead meat.
When I read Liam's script,
I thought,
"Wait! There's something I can change."
I can make your movie better.
So Queenie, show them the wardrobe
I handpicked for the female lead.
Straight from Paris, Mademoiselle.
These are the outfits for the scenes
where the couple is still happy.
Flowy, romantic dress.
I'll wear it if you don't want it, Miss Joyce.
Via, isn't this too much? I feel shy.
I'm actually forcing Liam
to include me in your project.
I'm the one embarrassed that
I'm forcing myself here.
It's not like that, love.
I just thought you were busy in Escale.
I'm not.
I want to join you in this project.
Is your dream exclusive
only for the two of you?
Of course not.
You're also part of my life...
of my... dreams.
So?
Does it mean the wardrobe I presented
is already approved,
Mr. Creative Manager?
Joyce, someone's looking for you.
Hans.
Hello.
Your boyfriend is good-looking.
True. That's true, Mama Tess.
Aunt Tess, this is Hans.
My friend.
He's a lawyer.
Hi, Attorney.
Hot-ttorney.
You two look good together.
You're like Liam and Via.
The chemistry is perfect.
What are you doing here?
Did you forget? You asked me to pick you up.
I'm so sorry I forgot.
Are you still finishing something?
It's okay. I can wait.
Are... are we done?
Yeah, I think so.
Joyce is already free, Hans.
Right, love?
Yeah, we're done.
We're finished.
Excuse me. Sorry. I need to take this call.
Via, I'm happy that you and Liam
will work together.
Me, too, Auntie. I'm glad he hired me.
You're more than capable, Via.
I even made a presentation and everything.
Okay, okay.
Thank you. Bye.
Hans, you're all good?
Liam...
Your family owns Casa Fuerte, right?
Yes. My dad is the CEO.
Why?
An accident happened at
your construction site.
Wait.
Oh, my God.
Accident?
Did someone die at Casa Fuerte?
Involving a construction worker.
My friend, what's going on?
I did what you told me.
I put some of the money in Casa Fuerte.
And some in Blacksmith.
We don't have a problem anymore.
It's all clean. We're now in the clear.
My friend, I did everything
you told me to do.
Someone saw you.
Boss, I have a family.
I won't talk.
We'll be dead if Big bro learns
that someone else saw us.
Big bro, I got of rid of him already.
Big bro.
You didn't cover your tracks.
- The construction worker...
- He's already dead, right?
He's alive!
And still breathing.
I should also kill people like you.
I'm surrounded by stupid people!
Don't.
Spare me, Ramon.
I'm a newbie.
That's why I need veterans.
This is Lando.
My most trusted gunman.
That face is the last thing you'll see
if you fail again, Danilo.
I won't call you if it's not urgent.
Anytime, Big bro.
Dear, why did you let Joyce
make an independent film?
Who will watch that?
I didn't allow her.
She's just stubborn.
Indie, my foot.
She won't make money off of that.
Correct.
And those who do independent films
are the has-beens.
Yes, there are awards.
But there's no money on that.
Correct.
- You won't gain profit from it.
- True.
Mommy, I have good news.
DigiTV has already agreed
to produce our indie film.
I hope you change your mind.
We need to talk.
Aren't you happy?
What's this?
[Falling Star?
Joyce A.K.A. Savana Dropped by Blacksmith]
You're still against it?
You won't support me?
Liam has poisoned your mind, hasn't he?
Oh my God!
Why did you have to get
the black sheep of the Herreras
for a boyfriend?
I wish you got Vergil instead.
Is this still about money?
Are you still thinking about money, Mom?
I noticed you always say that to me.
What do you take me for? Greedy for money?
This is not about money.
This is about your career.
Do you believe that's what people think?
Look at the comment section.
They're bashing you.
I am tired of pleasing people, Mom!
I'm so sick of it.
I don't care about what they think.
I don't care about what they say.
I'm old enough.
I can think on my own, Mom.
I'm so tired of being controlled,
on how to portray this and that.
I don't want anyone telling me
to say things against my will.
I'm so tired, Mom,
of being told to believe stories
that I can't find any worth.
That's the reason I cannot let go of you.
Because I can see that you're still immature.
Remember this.
You stepped on me,
that's why you're not on the ground.
You wouldn't have all of this
if it wasn't for me.
That's why all your decisions
should go through me.
Fine.
I will let you indulge in your craziness.
But the next time you sign a contract,
you will sign it
even if it comes from a demon!
What happened?
I don't need you in my movie.
There are lots of women
prettier and sexier than you.
Director, wait.
What happened?
Wait. Wait, Director.
I will talk to my daughter.
Joyce, why did he get mad at you?
Did he really have the guts to get mad, Mom?
He harassed me!
Joyce! I did everything to get you a slot
in this audition.
Come on!
You haven't had projects for a long time now.
Our savings are gone.
You should just put up with it.
So that means...
you know he's a pervert?
Come on, Joyce!
If you can't swallow things like that,
I don't know how to make you famous anymore!
Why, Mom? Am I not capable?
Am I not that good to you?
Can't I decently get a job?
Joyce, stay here.
Wait for me.
I'll talk to the director.
I will ask him to let you audition.
But I'll be there. I will look out for you.
You can do this.
You can do this. Wait for me.
Director! Director!
Where were we?
Hi, hello.
Oh, dear. Are you okay?
Yeah, of course.
We're okay too.
You know me, right?
I'm glad you met with me.
Dad...
I know I caused big trouble
when I left Casa Fuerte and Blacksmith.
So I'll understand
if you see me as a big disappointment.
But I am here because I'm worried about you.
Dad, please tell me.
What happened to the construction worker
who got into an accident?
Liam, it's out of your concern.
You said so yourself.
You abandoned me when you left Casa Fuerte.
So, please...
Please stop doing the wrong things.
Wrong?
What's right and wrong when
someone's life is on the line?
My friend, I did everything
you told me to do.
This is Lando.
My most trusted gunman.
That face is the last thing you'll see
if you fail again, Danilo.
The construction worker was sleeping
at the site without permission, Liam.
But someone told me he was shot.
Please.
I don't want to fight over this.
Casa Fuerte will pay for all the expenses
needed for his recovery.
I really hope you're okay, Dad.
Dad, it's not too late.
For you, for us.
We can still break free
from Congressman Ramon.
Liam...
I know I wasn't the best father
for you and your brother.
But someday...
you'll understand...
that I became a father the way I know how.
What do you want? Bihon or Palabok?
- Palabok.
- Here you go.
- Excuse me, here's the barbecue.
- Oh, wow!
- Let me have it.
Give it to me.
Come on. Hurry up. Pass it to them.
So we can refill it again.
- Okay. Wait, wait.
- Let's put some...
Hey, why did you get all of it?
Are you hungry, Borj?
Auntie, thank you so much.
Thank you so much for the food.
It's a pre-filming celebration for us.
It's nothing.
This is our advanced victory party.
But I notice you're quiet today.
Aren't you excited about tomorrow?
I'm excited.
Maybe I'm just tired.
You'll finish it.
You have a good team.
Just be professional,
and don't take it personally.
- It's good.
- I want an egg.
Do you like kids too?
I'm an only child.
But I dream of having a big family.
You and Liam are the same.
Solo.
Oh, he's not alone.
I forgot he has a brother.
But he's stubborn.
Try this.
Try the barbecue.
Thank you.
Sir Liam, can I borrow your phone?
Oh, this boy.
Auntie, this is so good.
What?
You make good barbecue.
You can win an award for this.
Oh, dear.
It really is good.
It's not in the sauce.
It depends on how long you marinate it...
just like relationships.
It gets better as it gets longer.
- That's my barbecue.
- Like Liam and Via.
They don't have the same attitude.
But they complement each other
as time goes by.
How about you?
How's your friend Hans?
Hans and I are both workaholics.
That's the case, Attorney.
His story isn't consistent.
He first told me
that there were other people that night.
And then he said he slipped.
Will you shut up?
Siloy, the lawyer's here already.
You don't have to be scared now.
Ma'am, Sir, it's okay if
you're not ready to talk yet.
No, Attorney.
Yes, my husband became disabled
because of the incident.
And we will lose our income.
But I'm not just after the money.
I want justice.
We both love working.
Is that so?
Why don't you give him a chance?
How will you know the taste
if you won't try it?
I'm going to try it, Auntie?
Auntie, I was shocked.
That's not what I meant.
Sorry.
What I mean is, give him a chance.
Who knows?
Right?
Oh, dear.
Hi, love.
- Auntie.
- Hi!
Hello.
Hello, too.
- Have a seat.
- Hi.
Give her a plate.
Miss Via...
Sir Liam, Miss Joyce, let's do TikTok.
I don't know how to do TikTok.
- I don't know how, too.
- I will teach you.
What are the steps?
I don't know how to dance.
What are we doing to do?
- Go ahead. Do it.
- I don't know how to do it.
Let's do TikTok.
- Is it easy?
- Come on, Miss Joyce.
Oh, no.
- I don't know how to do it.
- Where are we going to do it?
Sep, let's just do something easy.
- Yes.
- He's going to teach them.
One, two, three, go!
Cupid's bow and arrow.
- He hit me.
- Do you want some, Via?
I'm already in love.
Miss Via, do you want to join us?
No, thanks.
I'm wearing high heels.
- You can't get tired, remember?
- Yeah.
- Let's finish the video.
- Get some rest first.
Miss Joyce, I'll get more views
because of you.
Are we going to...
Fine.
- You're getting sweaty.
- You need to rest. You can't get tired.
Cupid's bow and arrow.
I think I fell in love with you.
You know what? Mom, join us.
I don't know how to do that.
Come on. Don't be shy.
I can see you're dancing.
Not really.
Come here.
Let's not do that. I don't know how to do it.
Auntie, I didn't know you liked TikTok.
You even do Zumba.
Hey, don't say that in front of your friends.
That's embarrassing.
Thank you, Grandma.
Are you happy?
Daddy, look. Balloons.
Balloons!
I didn't bring money with me.
I'll buy it.
Come here. How many do you want?
Three.
Go on and pick. What color do you want?
Red.
- Red.
- I want three of them.
My grandchild wants the red balloons.
Mister, three red balloons, please.
Here it is. Keep the change, okay?
Thank you, Grandma.
You're welcome, my grandson.
- Are you happy?
- Mama Tess, thank you.
I love you, Grandma.
I love you.
I love you too.
Are you now happy with your balloons?
Yes.
Mom?
Mom. Mom.
Mom, are you okay?
What happened?
I'm okay, son.
- What?
- I just felt a bit dizzy.
Do you want me to bring you to the hospital?
No, there's no need. I'm okay.
- You look like you need...
- Continue what you're doing.
I'll just take some rest.
Auntie, are you okay?
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
Guys, sorry.
I think I should bring my mom home.
Go ahead, Liam.
We'll take care of everything here.
It's okay.
Aunt Tess, are you really okay?
Yeah.
Yes, son. I think you should bring me home.
I'll get some rest at home.
Okay.
We can't talk to anyone from Casa Fuerte.
What will you do with justice
if it brings you trouble?
That's why Attorney's here.
Maybe I should come back some other day.
It's okay.
Attorney, I'm sorry for wasting your time.
No.
You don't have to apologize.
It's okay. Get well soon.
Just call me when you're ready to talk.
Thank you.
I'll get going, Sir.
Ma'am, I can see
that your husband doesn't want to talk.
And I understand
because I'm a stranger to him.
But I'll do what I can
to find out what really happened.
I'll find out if someone has to pay
for what happened to your husband.
Thank you, Attorney. I'll count on you.
Okay. Just call me.
- I'll get going.
- Be safe. Thank you.
You can leave me alone, son.
This is getting offensive.
I'm still young.
Mom, we're not talking about age here.
But your health.
How about it? Let's go to the hospital?
You're so serious.
Maybe I just got dizzy
because it was so hot at the park earlier.
That's all.
You're so stubborn.
I give up.
But you know what, son?
Earlier...
I felt like I was dreaming.
I saw you...
Joyce...
and Sep.
You and Joyce are husband and wife.
You're a family.
W-What's that? Am I hallucinating?
Or you were so focused
on Joyce and Sep earlier.
That's why?
Come on, Mom.
Maybe you've watched too many drama series.
And Joyce already has Hans.
And I...
You have Via.
Okay. Maybe I really should get some rest.
Go on, Mom.
Go to sleep now.
I'll stay here. I'll watch over you.
Go on, you can leave. I'm okay.
Close your eyes now.
Oh, boy.
Welcome back to my private resort.
Mayor, thank you so much
for letting us film here.
I can't say no to Via.
And speaking of Via...
I'm so sorry we're late.
Why do you look so surprised?
Sir Liam's script is really something.
It feels like it can move mountains.
It shows that he's so in love.
The question is, with whom is he in love?
Even the happiest film ends.
I heard that Siloy is dead.
What the...
Joyce, where are you?
Your dad collapsed in his house.